<?xml version="1.0"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="configuration.xsl"?>

<!-- Put site-specific property overrides in this file. -->

<configuration>

<property>
  <name>http.agent.name</name>
  <value>kien</value>
  <description>HTTP 'User-Agent' request header. MUST NOT be empty - 
  please set this to a single word uniquely related to your organization.

  NOTE: You should also check other related properties:

    http.robots.agents
    http.agent.description
    http.agent.url
    http.agent.email
    http.agent.version

  and set their values appropriately.

  </description>
</property>

<property>
  <name>generate.max.count</name>
  <value>10</value>
  <description>The maximum number of urls in a single
  fetchlist.  -1 if unlimited. The urls are counted according
  to the value of the parameter generator.count.mode.
  </description>
</property>

<property>
  <name>generate.min.interval</name>
  <value>0.7</value>
  <description>Select only entries with a retry interval lower than
  generate.min.interval. A value of -1 disables this check.</description>
</property>

<property>
  <name>plugin.folders</name>
  <value>/Users/kien/git/nutch/trunk_new/runtime/local/plugins</value>
  <description>Directories where nutch plugins are located.  Each
  element may be a relative or absolute path.  If absolute, it is used
  as is.  If relative, it is searched for on the classpath.</description>
</property>

<property>
  <name>scoring.conf.filename</name>
  <value>/Users/kien/git/nutch/trunk_new/topic.cfg</value>
  <description>path to the configuration file of the page classifier</description>
</property>

<property>
  <name>plugin.includes</name>
  <value>protocol-http|urlfilter-regex|parse-(html|tika)|index-(basic|anchor)|indexer-solr|scoring-pageclassifier|urlnormalizer-(pass|regex|basic)</value>
  <description>Regular expression naming plugin directory names to
  include.  Any plugin not matching this expression is excluded.
  In any case you need at least include the nutch-extensionpoints plugin. By
  default Nutch includes crawling just HTML and plain text via HTTP,
  and basic indexing and search plugins. In order to use HTTPS please enable
  protocol-httpclient, but be aware of possible intermittent problems with the
  underlying commons-httpclient library.
  </description>
</property>
</configuration>
